RG 062:140, Town of Thomaston
Connecticut State Library
Town of Thomaston records
1875-1936
Connecticut State Library
Thomaston (Conn.)
9 cubic feet
Tax records for the town of Thomaston.
RG062_140
T000603
Historical Note
The town of Thomaston was incorporated in July 1875 and was taken from Plymouth.
Scope and Content
Tax records for the town of Thomaston.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Thomaston -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Thomaston -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Thomaston -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Thomaston -- Registers
Places:
Thomaston (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1875-1936
  - Tax abstracts
    Volumes for 1911 to 1936 are not boxed.
    - 1875, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1879 (Box Box 1)
    - 1880, 1881, 1882, 1883 (Box Box 2)
    - 1884, 1885, 1886, 1887 (Box Box 3)
    - 1888, 1889, 1890, 1891 (Box Box 4)
    - 1892, 1893, 1894, 1895, 1896 (Box Box 5)
    - 1897, 1898, 1899, 1900, 1901 (Box Box 6)
    - 1902, 1903, 1904, 1905, 1906 (Box Box 7)
    - 1907, 1908, 1909, 1910 (Box Box 8)
    - 1911, 1 volume
    - 1912, 1 volume
    - 1913, 1 volume
    - 1914, 1 volume
    - 1915, 1 volume
    - 1916, 1 volume
    - 1917, 1 volume
    - 1918, 1 volume
    - 1919, 1 volume
    - 1920, 1 volume
    - 1921, 1 volume
    - 1922, 1 volume
    - 1923, 1 volume
    - 1924, 1 volume
    - 1925, 1 volume
    - 1926, 1 volume
    - 1927, 1 volume
    - 1928, 1 volume
    - 1929, 1 volume
    - 1930, 1 volume
    - 1931, 1 volume
    - 1932, 1 volume
    - 1933, 1 volume
    - 1934, 1 volume
    - 1935, 1 volume
    - 1936, 1 volume